(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-09-04T23:25:52.935998",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
hololive English -Advent- 2nd Anniversary Live "On the Run!"
It's Ollie's holoplus ZOM-RAID TIME
hololive English 3rd Concert "ALL FOR ONE"
Attention For Visitors
In-Stock Merch: Essentials Pack
In-Stock Merch: Light Stick & T-Shirt
Made-To-Order Merch: Random Button Badge
Made-To-Order Merch: Acrylic Stand Coaster
Made-To-Order Merch: Tapestry, Acrylic Panel & Mug
Made-To-Order Merch: Happi
Fan Messages
hololive English -Advent- 2nd Anniversary Live "On the Run!"
Ooh...
Just look around and see—it's so incredible!
So many smiles in a sea of light
Take one step with me and you'll be dazzled
There's magic in the air tonight
The hours zoom zoom zoom
My heart goes boom boom boom
The world is brighter because you believe in me
Let's shout it loud loud loud
Our time is right now
We're on the edge of destiny
For a moment, I can dream with you
Every miracle we hoped for might come true
We come together, reaching out from far and wide
And suddenly, you're here by my side!
When our voices and hearts unite, we're gonna shine bright!
Together, we're all for one
Let's sing! All for one!
The thrill of happiness is all around us!
Jump in, 'cause it's all for one
Let's sing! All for one!
We're on our way to good times, good vibes
We'll treasure this day the rest of our lives
Hey!
All that we waited for, the dream we're striving toward
We're singing, all for one!
All for one!
Everything's in motion
Get up and start the celebration
Come see the wonders here beyond imagination
We're joining hands for the world to see
Feel the love and the energy!
The hours zoom zoom zoom
My heart goes boom boom boom
A dizzy whirlwind of dreams and reality
Let's shout it loud loud loud
Our time is right now
We're here together, finally!
Every moment takes my breath away
There's a feeling here that words cannot convey
We hear the rhythm and we rise to meet the song
And suddenly, our hearts beat as one!
Every voice ringing loud and clear, so glad to be here
Together, we're all for one
Let's sing! All for one!
We'll sing in harmony and we'll be happy
Jump in, 'cause it's all for one
Let's sing! All for one!
Keep up the hype, it's good times, good vibes
Remember this night the rest of our lives
Hey!
Raise up your hands and sway, your light will lead our way
We're shining, all for one!
All for one!
So bring your memories, your joy and your hope
We'll gather and we'll sing upon this endless road, oh, oh
Feel the music in your passionate soul
We're here right now, so let the good times roll, oh, oh
Every time that I'm with you
I could swear it's like a wish is coming true
So I'll believe in you if you believe in me
Together we can chase all our dreams!
One, two, three, four, five!
When our voices and hearts unite, we're gonna shine bright!
Together, we're all for one
Let's sing! All for one!
The thrill of happiness is all around us!
Jump in, 'cause it's all for one
Let's sing! All for one!
We're on our way to good times, good vibes
We'll treasure this day the rest of our lives
Hey!
All that we waited for, the dream we're striving toward
We're singing, all for one!
All for one!
On the Run! hololive English -Advent- 2nd Anniversary Live
Zom-Raid Time
ALL FOR ONE hololive English 3rd Concert
Attention For Visitors
In-Stock Merch
Made-To-Order Merch
Fan Messages
ALL FOR ONE x HYTE
WAH!
Good Morning, Afternoon, and Evening! It's me, Ina!
I hope everyone is excited for the concert! I know I am!
I've been AmiAmi's ambassador for a full year now,
and it's been so much fun sharing all the great memories and the cool merch with you!
I've been using AmiAmi for a long time, but I still get excited every time I spot something WAHnderful on AmiAmi
- it's like finding treasure!
Whenever you find cute merch of your oshi on AmiAmi,
be sure to let us know, okay?
Let's give AmiAmi a big thank you for everything they've done this year!
Everyone say, Thank you AmiAmi!
Anyways, let's make more amazing memories tonight!
Make sure to cheer with everything you've got, okay?
WAH!
It's Ollie's holoplus ZOM-RAID TIME
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon. Please wait a moment.
Attention For Visitors
In-Stock Merch
Made-To-Order Merch
hololive English 3rd Concert - ALL FOR ONE -
Mori Calliope
MYTH
Mori Calliope / Takanashi Kiara / Ninomae Ina'nis
Hakos Baelz
Promise
IRyS / Ouro Kronii / Hakos Baelz
Shiori Novella
Nerissa Ravencroft
ADVENT
Shiori Novella / Koseki Bijou / Nerissa Ravencroft / Fuwawa Abyssgard / Mococo Abyssgard
Gigi Murin
JUSTICE
Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame / Gigi Murin / Cecilia Immergreen / Raora Panthera
Welcome to hololive English 3rd Concert, ALL FOR ONE!
Let's start with a bang!
ALL FOR ONE!
Just look around and see, it's so incredible!
So many smiles in a sea of light
Take one step with me and you'll be dazzled,
There's magic in the air tonight
The hours zoom zoom zoom
My heart goes boom boom boom
The world is brighter because you believe in me
Let's shout it loud loud loud
Our time is right now
We're on the edge of destiny
For a moment, I can dream with you
Every miracle we hoped for might come true
We come together, reaching out from far and wide,
And suddenly, you're here by my side!
When our voices and hearts unite, we're gonna shine bright!
Together, we're all for one.
Let's sing! All for one!
The thrill of happiness is all around us!
Jump in, 'cause it's all for one
Let's sing! All for one!
We're on our way to good times, good vibes
We'll treasure this day the rest of our lives
Hey!
All that we waited for, the dream we're striving toward,
We're singing, all for one!
All for one!
Everything's in motion,
Get up and start the celebration,
Come see the wonders here beyond imagination
We're joining hands for the world to see
Feel the love and the energy!
The hours zoom zoom zoom
My heart goes boom boom boom
A dizzy whirlwind of dreams and reality
Let's shout it loud loud loud
Our time is right now
We're here together, finally!
Every moment takes my breath away;
There's a feeling here that words cannot convey,
We hear the rhythm and we rise to meet the song,
And suddenly, our hearts beat as one!
Every voice ringing loud and clear, so glad to be here
Together, we're all for one.
Let's sing! All for one!
We'll sing in harmony and we'll be happy
Jump in, 'cause it's all for one
Let's sing! All for one!
Keep up the hype, it's good times good vibes
Remember this night the rest of our lives
Hey!
Raise up your hands and sway, your light will lead our way,
We're shining, all for one!
All for one!
So bring your memories, your joy and your hope,
We'll gather and we'll sing upon this endless road, oh, oh
Feel the music in your passionate soul,
We're here right now, so let the good times roll, oh, oh
Every time that I'm with you,
I could swear it's like a wish is coming true
So I'll believe in you if you believe in me,
Together we can chase all our dreams!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5!
When our voices and hearts unite, we're gonna shine bright!
Together, we're all for one.
Let's sing! All for one!
The thrill of happiness is all around us!
Jump in, 'cause it's all for one
Let's sing! All for one!
We're on our way to good times, good vibes
We'll treasure this day the rest of our lives
Hey!
All that we waited for, the dream we're striving toward,
We're singing, all for one!
All for one!
Nerissa Ravencroft
Shiori Novella
Koseki Bijou
Fuwawa Abyssgard
Mococo Abyssgard
Time to open up your eyes,
Feel the music start to rise,
Got to break the world and let me in.
I know I was meant to be
Livin' life so fast and free, try to keep your eyes on me,
'cause this is where my story all begins!
We're gonna make you...
...make you crazy
Ready to play, come at me
Clear the way, so easy
I can't get enough
Raise the bar, no limit
Can you hear it and feel it?
Here we go, let's do this
Watch me, watch me, watch me, watch me
Watch me be your diva
I'm gonna raise your fever
Shaking up all the crowd
Making some noise when I'm not allowed
Living my life out loud
I have awakened to wisdom beyond all understanding
I keep indulging in my head, oh
Ah-ah-ah...
Don't blame me if I shine too bright
Can't help it if I start a fight
Ah-ah-ah...
Now pay attention, kid
'Cause this is only the beginning
It's our genesis!
Call me unique, some have it
How do you like this goddess?
I'm embracing my madness
Can you hear it?
Whispers banging down your window
Rumors reaching a crescendo
No humble beginning, I'm destined for great things
I'm sure you have heard of me by now
Midnight, dramatic to the dark side
Starlight, take me on a joyride
My crime is my passion
Mayhem in action
I know what day it is
This is our genesis!
Ah...
I'm gonna start a raid, why not misbehave, take center stage?
Let the fun commence, but you know I'm gonna get intense
A vow unspoken
The rules can all be broken
And running on a rampage
With nowhere else left to play
I'm writing my story in flames and in glory
They're gonna know me by name
Ah-ah-ah...
Is this my promised land?
The future's in my hand
Ah-ah-ah...
But they don't understand
That I'm a sign of the making, awaking, and taking
All of, all of, all of, all of
Tell me how you like me now!
Show, show, show, show, show!
Come on!
Watch me, watch me, watch me, watch me
Let your worries go
I'm gonna show you how to lose control, ready?
You can go free your mind
Leave your restrictions behind
Be outrageous
The chaos is contagious
Come on, you know what time it is
It's our genesis!
Chant it, open up your eyes
Feel the music start to rise
Got to break the world and let me in
I heard a voice meant to be
Living life so fast and free
Try to keep your eyes on me
'Cause this is our beginning
It's our genesis!
Whispers banging down your window
Rumors reaching a crescendo
No humble beginning, I'm destined for great things
I'm sure you have heard of me by now
Midnight, dramatic to the dark side
Starlight, take me on a joyride
My crime is my passion
Mayhem in action
I know what day it is
This is our genesis!
It's our genesis!
Tell me what time it is, it's our genesis!
Yeah, you know what time it is, it's our genesis!
Ninomae Ina'nis
さあ 散らばってしまった話を
Now, about the story that was scattered...
空に手を伸ばし始める
I will start reaching my hand out to the sky.
そっと 移り過ぎる瞬きに
Gently, in the flickering of passing moments,
縛られた足をくすぐるの
it tickles my bound feet.
あぁ 落ちてゆく汚れた意識を
Ah, as my stained consciousness falls down,
甘い微睡みとすり替えて
substituting it with a sweet slumber.
空っぽだった身体の
Of this body that was once empty,
夢見ていた瞼が開く
the eyelids that were dreaming now open.
心の奥から うごめく記憶が
From deep within my heart, a stirring memory...
混ぜた呪いと祈りの
The mixed curses and prayers...
リガメントの藍を捨てるの
I cast away their indigo ligament.
始まりと終わりに向かって
Toward the beginning and the end...
螺旋に描いてくるのは
Drawing in a spiral...
八方の呼び声だけ
is only the calling from all directions.
あなた そこにいたら教えてほしいの
If you are there, I want you to tell me...
私が歩くこの道はどんな色だろう
what color this path I walk is.
ああ この調べの旋律を
Ah, this melody of the tune...
空に手を伸ばし始める
begins to reach its hand toward the sky.
散らばった 多くの血の道が
The scattered paths of much blood...
愛を欲して 泣き叫んでる
are crying and screaming, desiring love.
始まりと終わりに向かって
Toward the beginning and the end...
螺旋に描いてくるのは
Drawing in a spiral...
救われなかった君の声
is your voice that could not be saved.
愛しい人よ そこにいたら教えて
My beloved, if you are there, tell me...
君の手をいつかまた握れるの この手で
Will I ever be able to hold your hand again with these hands?
Yeah! New York!
New York! New York!
New York!
You good? You good? You good?
I'm good.
Okay. I'm good.
You good? We good!
It's finally time. We are here. We are here!
We are here!
Well, shall we?
We shall. You go first.
I go first? You go first. Okay.
You know the drill, guys!
I say "wah", you say "wah"! Wah!
Good morning, afternoon, evening! This is Ninomae Ina'nis of Hololive English...
You got this, you got this!
I just did a song, I'm tired!
Okay, and we have...
What's up?!
I am chaos, the end of times,
the steel rat trapped in a cage of ice,
your worldwide idol, Hakos Baelz of Hololive English Promise! Witness me!
Guys! How was that for an opener?
Did you guys enjoy it?
I can't hear you!
And of course, everyone watching from home. Hello!
We see you guys! We see you! Hello, hello!
Ah, yeah. We have arrived at EN's 3rd live, All For One.
Ina, how do you feel?
I feel... fantastic!
Fantastic.
I feel fantastic.
Miraculously preserved.
You know, I can't believe it's already the third live.
First, we Connected the World.
Second, we Broke the Dimension.
And third, we are...
ALL FOR ONE!
Did you guys like...? I guess this is the first time we're all together performing "All for One".
Yeah.
Yeah. Oh man, I almost cried.
I know. And I was like...
Oh my god, so emotional.
But I hope you guys enjoyed the opener, we had Advent...
...and then we had Ina's solo.
That was so good! Did you guys like it?
Oh my goodness!
All right, you know, since this is the very... the first...
This is the first MC of the first day...
Of the first day! We're just getting started.
We're just getting started. We need to test those penlights.
Yeah, test the penlights! All right.
Blue, red, white...
How about we split down the middle here...
...and we go... purple? No, not purple. Violet!
Violet here, and...
And red...
And red over here! I wanna see red!
Oh my goodness, I always get so emotional...
...seeing the sea of penlights.
Oh yeah.
And not only that, you know, we're just getting started.
There's a whole show today and tomorrow.
So make sure to share it, share your excitement...
...with the hashtag #holoAllforOne! Post it!
Ready to do the next part? Do I get to do the next part?
Fine, I'll let you do it this time.
Okay! Although it is kind of sad news...
Well, wait, it's just I've never done it before. I'm really excited, but...
She's excited, but it's kind of sad because...
...it is now time to announce that...
I have terrible news!
Oh! What is it, Hakos Baelz?
Unfortunately, if you are watching from home...
...this is the end of the free segment!
How could this be? Absolute tragedy!
This is a tragedy, but do not worry.
If you are at home and you just saw this bang-up opening...
...and you want to continue watching the rest of the concert...
...check the link in the description, get your tickets, and continue watching the concert!
Not you guys, you guys are stuck here until the end.
You're not going anywhere, all right.
You guys better be ready with your unlimited energy.
Yeah, I think we should test a little bit.
Are you guys ready?
All right, you know the drill.
Do they know the drill? Do I know the drill?
You know the drill.
I know the drill.
All right, count down from three!
Three, two, one...
ALL FOR ONE!
[Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame]
[Cecilia Immergreen]
[Gigi Murin]
[Raora Panthera]
[The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.]
無料パートは終了いたしました！
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview has ended!
Thank you for watching!
無料パートは終了いたしました！
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview has ended!
Thank you for watching!
無料パートは終了いたしました！
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview has ended!
Thank you for watching!
無料パートは終了いたしました！
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview has ended!
Thank you for watching!
無料パートは終了いたしました！
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview has ended!
Thank you for watching!